[Music]
[Música]
Can I send Sasel the
le puedo yo mandar a a sasel la
invitation to upload it? Wait, how
invitación a Que suba espérate cómo le
can I send Sasel the invitation to
puedo mandar a sasel la invitación a Que
upload it? Aiden, do you have contact with Sasel?
suba aiden tú tienes contacto con sasel
Aiden, do you have contact with Sasel?
aiden tú tienes contacto con sasel
Because we could have done this?
Porque podríamos ha
Why was this removed? Why was
así Por qué se ha quitado esto por qué
this removed? Let's see. I'm going to, I'm going to,
se ha quitado esto a ver
Sasel. Wait, I'm going to, I'm going to see
voy voy sacel Espera voy a voy a ver
how I can send you Give me a second
cómo te logro mandar Dame un segundito
please give me a
por favor dame un
second Give me a second because of course we did
segundito Dame un segundito porque claro
n't have it prepared But in a
no lo teníamos preparado Pero en un
second we'll get you in without any problem don't
segundo te metemos sin problema no te
worry if you manage to have a
preocupes si logras una batalla de
bald battle here on your channel right now I'll
calvos aquí en tu canal ahora mismo yo
give you 500 bucks seriously ball let's see
te dono 500 pavos en serio bolita a ver
man keep your word because the
hombre cumple con tu palabra porque la
truth is that what I
verdad es que a mí lo que me
would like would be for them to get to
gustaría sería que llegasen a llegase
talk clearly would be what I would
hablar claro sería lo que a mí me
like but not because you give me the
gustaría pero ya no porque tú me des la
money that you also have to give it to me
pasta que también me la tienes que dar
but because one second Sasel one second I'm
sino porque un segundo sacele un segundo
going to try to send you the
que voy intentar hacerte llegar el
link so you can upload it if I can I'm
enlace para que subas si consigo Yo
also worth it I already have the camera
también vale Yo ya tengo la cámara
set up here and I only have  that
puesta por aquí y solo tengo que
getting
conseguir que
those have the link okay second
esas tenga el enlace vale segundito
aidem help me
aidem ayúdame
aidem Javi the images are the video d d
aidem Javi las imagnes son el víde d d
responds to Claro but it's that it can't
le responde a Claro pero es que eso no
be like they say you don't have to
puede ser así como dice tú no le tienes
ask someone's permission to
que pedir permiso a alguien para para
use images one second what's
que se utilicen unas imágenes un segundo
this Okay then Now I just
que ajo esto Vale pues Ahora solamente
need to send sasel the
faltaría hacerle llegar a sasel el
link I'm going to see if aiden can send it to him
enlace voy a ver si aiden se lo puede
how do I send him the link okay let's
llegar cómo le mando el enlace vale a
see luares
ver luares
okay sasel They're going to send you the link through
vale sasel Te van a mandar el enlace por
Instagram okay They're going to send you the link through Instagram sasel it's going to
Instagram vale Te van a mandar el enlace
reach you now they're going
por Instagram sasel te va a llegar ahora
to send you now the kids through
te van a mandar ahora los chavales por
Instagram the link okay it's that I didn't
Instagram el enlace vale es que no la
have the call ready Sorry doesn't
tenía preparada la llamada Perdóname no
have Instagram does it have open mds on
tiene Instagram tiene los md abiertos de
Twitter if it was like that Javi let's see I'm going to
Twitter si fue así Javi a ver voy a
look for an email I'm going to look for an email of course yes
buscar un email voy a buscar un email es
if I put the link in
que claro si si le pongo el enlace en
public they're going to come in here 28 million
público yo van a entrar aquí 28 millones
here wait wait I have it I have it I have it I have it I have it I have it I have it I have it I have it I have it on
aquí espérate espera lo tengo lo tengo
Twitter I have it on Twitter okay I have it I have it  I have it
Twitter lo tengo en Twitter vale lo
on Twitter I have
tengo lo tengo lo tengo en Twitter tengo
it I have it on Twitter already upload to
lo tengo lo tengo en Twitter ya subes a
already upload
ya subes
to okay already upload already upload I'm going to mute
a vale ya sube ya sube voy a silenciar
the notifications okay so you don't
las notificaciones vale para que no
interrupt the conversation it's over
interrumpas la conversación ya está por
here a second I'll reflect the camera
aquí un segundo que reflejo la cámara
so you can see it well Now what's up
para que se vea bien Ahora qué pasa
good afternoon how are we no we can't
buenas tardes cómo estamos no no te
hear you down there you have
escuchamos ahí por ahí abajo tienes
microphone sound settings Ah now
configuración sonido micrófono Ah ahora
what's up man Good afternoon what
sí Qué pasa tío Buenas tardes qu ha
happened don't you see no the deal No well well
pasado no ve no la movida No pues bueno
as you can understand well then
como tú podrás comprender pues des luego
a deal if you want I'll
que una movida si quieres te voy
explain to you I'll explain to your
explicando le voy explicando a tu
audience what
público qué es lo que ha sucedido
exactly happened Yeah sure There's something in between
exactamente Sí claro Hay algo por medio
that we might have left out or something like that
que nos hayamos dejado o algo por el
But I understand that
estilo Pero entiendo que ya cuando
when Sergio got like this this
cuando Sergio se ha puesto así este
last click something is missing no Yes that that's what
último click falta algo no Sí eso eso lo
concerns a white guy that I
que atañe con un tío blanco etero que me
was freaking out with this guy I was freaking out
he quedado flipando con este tipo Me he
with this eh And then with
quedado flipando con este eh Y luego con
l Eulogio let's see me with l Eulogio we have never
l Eulogio a ver yo con l Eulogio nunca
not spoken to each other there has never
no hemos dirigido la palabra nunca ha
been a bad word towards him and my
habido una mala palabra hacia él y mi
girlfriend neither so it was very
novia tampoco entonces fue muy
surprising when in his live on
sorprendente cuando en su directo del 24
February 24th he says  the atrocities he
de febrero dice las barbaridades que
says about Maria, besides
dice sobre María además
affirming the vocabulary, it's not invented, that he's
afirmándolo vocabulario no es invent que
really doing that with another
de verdad está haciendo eso con otro
guy so and so, I'm freaking out
tipo tal y cual yo me quedo flipando
because on top of that, the
porque es que encima el presentador
current presenter of PlayStation Spain, which seems like
actual de PlayStation españ que parece
nonsense but for me it
una chorrada pero que para mí desde
certainly isn't nonsense Because if a
luego no es una chorrada Porque si una
person who is a presenter of
persona que es presentadora de
PlayStation Spain reaches such a level
PlayStation España llega hasta tal nivel
of hatred to say such an atrocity in one of his live broadcasts
de odio a decir esa barbaridad en un
Well, with that level of
directo suyo Pues con ese grado de
influence you say Well, these people, I don't
influencia dices tú Bueno esta gente no
really know the trap they're
sé muy bien la trampa en la que me está
putting me in Well, yes, that's it For example, seo really
metiendo Bueno sí eso Por ejemplo seo te
emphasized that you should put
hacía mucho hincapié en que tú pusiera
presenter and I explained it Here these
presentador y yo lo explicaba Aquí esta
people, I don't know if he was still there in the chat
gente no s si estaba por ahí por el chat
but it is important
todavía pero es que sí es importante
let's see if Jorge Javier suddenly
vamos a ver si Jorge Javier de repente
Jorge Javier Vasque starts putting on his
Jorge Javier vasque pone a poner en su
Twitter account I [ __ ] on [ __ ]
cuenta de Twitter me cago en [__]
dead people, disgusting [ __ ], [ __ ], whether you like it or
muertos [__] asquerosa [__] quieras
not, Tele5 is going to give him a sniff, is it going
que no tele5 le van a pegar un toque va
to say that you are the visible face of
a decir yo que eres la cara visible
us right now cut it out Then yes, he
nuestra ahora mismo córtate Entonces sí
has In fact, I think that even
que tiene De hecho yo creo que incluso
those apologies that have been a
esas disculpas que han sido para mí un
little weak for me, I don't know if  to you guys it will have been
poco flojilla no sé si a ustedes habrán
worth it for me it has been a little
valido para mí ha sido un poco también
carried away by the fact that he is
llevadas por el hecho de que de que está
currently working at Sony yes and and I
ahora mismo trabajando en Sony sí y y te
tell you my brother Hachi spoke in his
comento mi hermano Hachi habló en su
chat and told him in a good way Hey you are
chat y le dijo de buenas maneras Oye que
getting old what are you doing
ya tiene una edad que está haciendo
messing with my brother's girlfriend and
metiéndote con la novia de mi hermano y
such they automatically expel you from the
tal automáticamente le expulsan del chat
low logio chat you know what there is with
del low logio ya sabes tú que está lo de
beto's evasion what you can
la evasión de beto lo de que puedes
send him a message and such to see what
ponerle un mensaje y tal para ver qué es
happened He sent a message to my
lo que ha pasado Le puso un mensaje a mi
brother saying But well I'm going
hermano diciendo Pero bueno me vay a mí
to press for this and such And what
a pulsar por este y tal Y lo que le
they put to him logio or I don't know if some
pusieron lo logio o no sé si algún
moderator was an XD I mean he already
moderador fue una XD O sea que él ya
knew he already knew from the second one that That
sabía él ya sabía desde el segundo uno
the subject is not funny it is not funny they
que Que gracia no hace el tema gracia no
invite him to the fizon of Granada
hace lo invitan para la fizon de granada
so I say well look I have
entonces digo yo bues mira yo hasta aquí
come this far I do not feel like crossing paths
he llegado yo no tengo ganas de cruzarme
with logio in the fizon after the
con el logio en las fizon después de las
atrocities that he has said And then I make
barbaridades que ha dicho Y entonces
a video on YouTube I make a
hago hago un vídeo en YouTube hago un
video on YouTube explaining this whole
vídeo en YouTube explicando toda esta
situation buo  eh before making the video
situación buo eh antes de hacer el vídeo
on YouTube you tell Eulogio on
en YouTube tu le digo yo al Eulogio por
Twitter Hey I really want to
Twitter Oye que tengo muchas ganas de
see you around Granada and he says to me
verte por aquí por Granada y él me dice
that if he looks for me he'll find me I
tranquilo que si me busca me encontrará
say I threaten no no and I
tal digo yo amenazas no no y le le tenía
really wanted to see him and I answer him
muchas ganas de verlo y le respondo
we're older or rather er I was like
somos mayores o sea er era en plan que
no but stop so he can explain his
no pero para para que me explique él sus
comments to me so he can explain his
comentarios para que me explique él sus
comments to me and I say no I'm not the only one going I'm not going
comentarios y digo no solo voy a ir no
alone my
voy a ir solo yo va a ir también mi
girlfriend is going too no a threat it's so that he'll be
novia no una amenaza es para que se le
embarrassed confront him
caiga la cara de vergüenza enfrentarlo
a little in the face I mean not threats of
un poco en cara o sea no amenazas de
hitting but but threats of cutting him
pegar pero pero si amenazas de pegarle
No confront him a little in the face let's see
un corte No enfrentarlo un poco en cara
how you explain to me what you
a ver a ver cómo me explicas tú lo que
said that to his face I tell him about my
has dicho eso a la cara le digo lo de mi
girlfriend and he says all of a sudden all of a sudden he sort of
novia y me dice ya de repente de repente
realizes and says Oy No no it's
como que se da cuenta y dice Oy No no es
that I think they came to you with a
que creo que te han venido con un
broken toy according to his own
juguete estropeado según su propia
word eh I think no no no there was
palabra eh creo que no no no ha habido
a misunderstanding and he pretty much says Come over
un malentendido y de sobrado dice Pásate
here if you want and I'll give you an
por aquí si quieres y te doy un
autograph  I'll give you an F and but he told you that yes yes he
autógrafo te hago una F y pero te dijo
is on Twitter he said it He
eso sí sí está en Twitter lo dijo Me lo
answered me on Twitter no no Come over and I
respondió en Twitter no no Pásate y te
'll sign you, I say man Of course
hago una firma digo yo hombre Claro que
champion I'll make the video with which I
sí campeón le hago el vídeo con el cual
put the extracts where he himself in his
pongo los extractos donde el mismo en su
live says the barbarities that he says
directo dice las barbaridades que dice
of course Twitch Spain has not acted
por supuesto Twitch España ni ha actuado
or absolutely anything there is no It's strange eh
ni absolutamente nada no hay Es raro eh
Because let's see, they are comments that are
Porque a ver son comentarios que son
bannable total what he said about Mara
baneables total lo que ha dicho de María
is bannable 100% a major lack of respect
es baneable 100% una falta de respeto
In addition, it is not only a lack
importante Además no es solo una falta
of respect but there are several crimes that they
de respeto sino que son varios delitos
commit and then we have the one who
los que cometen y y luego tenemos el el
logically has a lot of trouble with me and they
que lo lógico que me tiene mucha gana y
pay attention to those videos that there are of
le hacen caso a esos vídeos que hay de
extracts from different of my live streams
extractos de diferentes directos míos en
where you can hear Mara in the background that she
donde se oye a María de fondo que sí que
was playing Fortnite at that
está jugando al fortnite en aquella
time with a friend of hers and to
época con un amigo suyo y que para
try to get attention on the
intentar llamar la atención en el Canal
live channel of her friend, Mara
de directo del amigo suyo pues María
raises her voices and many screams you already know
pega la voces y muchos grito tú ya sabes
that I have many haters behind them they collect
que tengo muchos hater detrás recogen
those images and they make the movie they
esas imágenes y ya se hacen la película
want and since there are many people
que quieren y ya como hay mucha gente
who have a hard time with me, they want  believe
que me tiene ganas pues quieren creerse
I have seen I don't know if I don't know at what point
yo he visto no sé si no sé en qué punto
of the live it arrived but when at the
del directo ha llegado pero cuando al
beginning I have seen it I was like
principio yo lo he visto yo me quedé que
yes they were moans and then I have cut
sí eran gemidos y y luego he recortado
the piece and I have started the
el trozo y he empezado de nuevo el
extract again because I have said I am going to start
extracto porque he dicho voy a empezar a
reacting to this again from scratch
reaccionar otra vez a esto de cero
because it would not seem fair to me that now
porque no me parecería justo que ahora
I start reacting from the
yo me ponga a reaccionar des el
beginning and there are people who do believe it
principio y haya gente que sí se lo crea
because in truth Of course you are
porque en verdad Claro tú te encuentras
on YouTube a click you are maybe
en YouTube un click estás tú a lo mejor
live and you can hear them in the background I
en directo y se escucha de fondo los
scream and it puts Sarcel's girlfriend in the title
grito y te pone de título la novia de
behind her I don't know what expensive sneak peek If
sarcel la atrá no sé qué caro cuela Si
you don't know each other if you don't follow your
tú no te conoces si tú no sigues tus
live streams they are telling me it's not that you
directos a mí me están diciendo no es
are an open couple I say Oh well
que son una pareja abierta digo Ah bueno
but maybe no no we are not an
pero igual no no no somos una pareja
open couple no they are not live streams they are videos of
abierta no no son directos son vídeos
mine uploaded to my YouTube channel and well
míos subidos mi canal de YouTube y bueno
And if that if it is
Y si eso si es lo que dices hubiesen
what you say they had been what you say it would have been at the moment and more people would have thought it but not everything comes from a snowball of haters uploading these videos Well on tiktok and things like that not in  reels or
en tiktok y en cosas así no en reels o
rather it's like information let's say it
sea es como información vamos a decirlo
like that decontextualized of course if
así descontextualizada claro si ya te
a hater comes to you first
viene a ti de primera un hater
putting you in the title Hey in moaning
poniéndote en el título Oye en gemido
such and such you automatically if you don't know
tal y cual tú automáticamente si no sabe
absolutely anything or is going to say Well yes it
absolutamente nada o va a decir Bueno sí
could be but they are simply gr Okay
podría ser pero son simplemente gr Vale
then well This is the situation and
entonces bueno Está la situación esta y
then I already praise him with the
luego ya lo elogio con las barbaridades
other atrocities that he says a series of
demás que dice que una serie de
atrocities that on the part of Eulogio and
barbaridades eso por parte de Eulogio y
now comes the subject of a straight white guy a
ahora llega el tema de un tío blanco
straight white guy of course
etero un tío blanco etero por supuesto
has all the freedom in the world as is
tiene toda la libertad del mundo como es
logical to talk about this subject
lógico de hablar sobre este tema Ya he
I have already uploaded a subject about praise he makes a
subido yo un tema sobre elogio hace un
comment that bothers me he makes a
comentario que me molesta hace un
comment that bothers me he says no
comentario que me molesta se pone no
well I'm not going to imitate him now
bueno no lo voy a imitar ahora
but the thing is that what he should do is
pero es que lo que debería hacer es
soundproof the walls I've seen and that
insonorizar las paredes hos visto y eso
bothers me because I say let's see I
a m me molesta porque digo yo a ver yo
'm living with Maria or rather because
estoy viviendo con María o sea porque se
any sound from Maria sneaks in does not
cuele cualquier sonido de María no
mean that they are moaning or
quiere decir que estén gimiendo ni
doing anything at all I mean you can't agree with him
haciendo nada de nada O sea tú no le
or go along with
puedes llevar la razón o llevar la
the haters I don't have to
corriente a los haters yo no tengo que
do anything the problem is  yours with what
hacer nada el problema es tuyo con lo
with what you want to interpret or what
que con lo que quieres interpretar o lo
because you want to play along with
que porque quieres seguirle el juego a
these people then a little bit like that and
esta gentuza entonces un poco eso no y
I was talking to him like that and then this straight white guy gets excited, he
yo le hablaba así y entonces un tío
gets excited but good And then
viene arriba pero bien Y entonces ya
during his live show he totally forgets
durante su directo se olvida totalmente
about the praise and wants to get into me, he
del elogio y se quiere entrar en mí que
gets all like that and I don't care
se pone así en ese plan y a mí me da ya
what each one thinks anymore I already
igual lo que le parezca a cada uno yo ya
say what it is that it is the reality the straight
digo lo que es que es la realidad el tío
white guy it really strikes me
blanco etero me llama mucho la atención
that during his live show he says more than 10
que durante su directo dice más de 10
times that my girlfriend is moaning more than
veces que mi novia está gimiendo más de
10 times, I mean he hasn't even
10 veces o sea no la ha llegado a
corrected her in these live shows after that in
corregir en estos directos después en
these answers that you have he doesn't say
estas respuesta que os habéis no dice
that he says that she is moaning eh but she
que dice que está gimiendo eh pero es
is moaning and he
que está gimiendo y lo recalca una y
emphasizes it over and over again more than 10 times simply because it angered him that I told him that and then on top of that he uses terminology like he used at the time low logio that says that my girlfriend is screaming in the
está pegando berridos en la habitación
next room and then I say Uh wait for
de al lado y ahí yo ya digo Uh Espérate
this  this is getting out of hand I don't
ya esto ya se está saliendo de madre no
know if some white guy
sé si es que un tío blanco etero me
wants to provoke me I don't really know what he's up to
quiere provocar no sé muy bien Qué es lo
and focusing on me and all
que pretende y centrándose en mí y toda
this [ __ ] and I'll make a video and I'll
esta chorrada y ya le hago yo un vídeo y
say Look, you said in the context in
le digo Mira has dicho en el contexto en
which we find ourselves, which is a
el que nos encontramos que un contexto
rather serious context, which is the case of
bastante grave que es el caso del
Eulogio, it's going to be the case of Eulogio, you
Eulogio va a ser el caso de Eulogio tú
make these statements 10 times without them
haces estas afirmaciones 10 veces sin
being the truth, which is why you are
que sean la verdad con lo cual está
making a kind of promotion, a
haciendo como una promoción una
rather improper association in the
asociación bastante indebida en el
context in which we are talking, in
contexto en el que estamos habl en ya en
those videos you have already clarified that
esos vídeos le has aclarado que era que
those screams that are heard from Maria
eso esos gritos que se escuchan de María
are from video games, that it's not such a thing And
que son de videojuegos que no es tal Y
then he takes it as Yes, yes,
entonces él se lo toma como Sí sí de
moans, no, like he doesn't believe it No, yes,
gemidos no como que no se lo cree No sí
that he is in an arrogant mood, he is in an
que él está en plan altivo ya él está en
arrogant mood and now he wants to provoke because it is
plan altivo y ya quiere provocar porque
obvious that he wants to provoke Because it is
se le nota que quiere provocar Porque se
clear that he has not liked me for a long time and and
ve que le caigo mal de hace tiempo y y
about the bellowing, I tell him that the
lo de los berridos le digo yo que el
bellowing is what deer do
berrido es lo que hacen los ciervos
during the rut, that
durante la berrea que no lo hacen los
human beings do not do it, no, no  you talk like that
seres humanos que no que no hables así
about my girlfriend take advantage of a white guy
sobre mi novia aprovecha un tío blanco
you know that she is my partner that she
etero ya sabes tú que es mi pareja que
is my girlfriend like It's logical man I
es mi novia como Es lógico hombre Yo
want to protect her like It's logical from
quiero protegerla como Es lógico de
teatropello from logio and from and from the
teatropello de logio y de y del de
presenter of PlayStation espaia
presentador de PlayStation espaia
So it's a topic that well I don't know about
Entonces es un tema que bueno no sé lo
inviting opinions it's that I don't really know how to
de invitar a opinión es que no sé muy
invite opinions on what Because
bien invitar a opinión de qué Porque
then there is the topic a parallel topic
luego está ya el tema un tema paralelo
that in which a white guy comes in
quee en el que entra un tío blanco etero
no no but it seems that you can hear the
no no pero es que parece que se oye a la
girlfriend no no no no it's that not the topic
novia no no no no es que ese no el tema
the topic is the atrocities that
el tema son las barbaridades que ha
Eulogio has said that are lies that
dicho el Eulogio que son mentiras que
are totally That is the topic and a
son totalmente Ese es el tema y un tío
white guy is focusing on my girlfriend that is what
blanco etero se centra en mi novia eso
bothers me I make the video I
es lo que a mí me molesta hago el vídeo
express it like this so that a white guy
lo Expreso así para que un tío blanco
will stop stop with that attitude you
etero pare pare con esa actitud tú
Sorry that I'm here at least you no no no
Perdona que esté aquí si quiera tú no no
no I was not
no no te estaba
listening to you I comment that So a
escuchando comento eso Entonces un tío
white guy uploaded the video yesterday This was
blanco etero subo el vídeo ayer Esto fue
yesterday in the afternoon and a white guy is going
ayer por la t tarde y un tío blanco
to react in his live and I
etero va a reaccionar en su directo y
say look I don't  I want this guy to
digo yo Mira yo no quiero que este tío
put my image in his live As
ponga mis imágen en su directo Tan
simple as that because I wanted him to
sencillo como eso porque quería
stop because the
precisamente que parase porque ya la
attitude is already in me You know that can't be
actitud me está Tú sabes que eso no se
avoided you may like it more or you
puede evitar te puede gustar más o te
may like it less but yes no but yes
puede gustar menos pero sí no pero sí
but it is copyrighted content from my
pero es contenido con copyright de mi
YouTube channel with which I do
canal de YouTube con lo cual sí que
have the right to do so I put it to him
tengo derecho a hacer entonces le puse
in the chat I don't give you permission to put
por el chat no te doy permiso para poner
my image in the single like that let's see
mi imagen en el sencillo como eso a ver
Javi tell me what what do you want no it's that I
Javi dime qué qué quieres no es que yo
don't agree with that and in fact
con eso no estoy de acuerdo y de hecho
I'm let's see apart it's that the
estoy a ver aparte es que entran las
YouTube rules come into play yesterday
normas de YouTube ayer precisamente
we had a kid who had the same thing happen to him
tuvimos un chaval que le pasó lo mismo
a kid but from the other theme that
un chaval pero de la otra temática que
I have on the telesalseo channels and he
yo tengo en los canales de telesalseo y
had a conflict with another creator that
tenía un conflicto con otro creador que
the other creator doesn't want people to talk
el otro creador no quiere que se hable
about the controversies that he has And then
de las polémicas que él tiene Y entonces
he threatened to strike him he tried to
lo amenazó con meterle strike le intentó
strike him in fact he tried to
com meter el strike de hecho le intentó
strike him and YouTube rejected it
meter los strike y YouTube se lo rechazó
because YouTube considered it to be
porque YouTube Consideró que era uso
fair use You know that sometimes it
legítimo Tú sabes que hay veces que
works and sometimes it doesn't So you
cuela y hay veces que no Entonces te
may like it more or you may like it less
puede gustar más o te puede gustar menos
but of course give permission that  in
pero claro dar permiso que en los
YouTube's terms they also warn you, also
términos de YouTube te lo avisan además
know that there are people who can
que sepas que hay personas que pueden
react to your content Although they don't
reaccionar a tu contenido Aunque a ti no
ask your permission, I'm clear of course
te pidan permiso me claro por supuesto
Yes, I understand annoyance eh I mean no yes I yes I
Sí yo entiendo molestia eh o sea no si
also yes I also
yo si yo también si yo la también la
understand it Javi Oliveira Sorry no yes I
entiendo Javi oliveira Perdona no si yo
have I understand what you're telling me
tengo Comprendo lo que me está diciendo
about the YouTube and Twitch rules, yes
de la norma de YouTube y de de Twitch si
I understand it, we're already talking in
yo lo comprendo ya estamos hablando en
another context Javi, we're talking about the
otro contexto Javi estamos hablando del
context of a trial, it's different from the one I don't care anymore, I don't care about
contexto de un juicio ya es distinto a
the YouTube rule and the Twitch rule
la regla de YouTube y la regla de Twitch
that I don't give you permission to put my
que no te doy permiso para ponerme
images do you want to sue
imagenes quieres a demandarlo tú a
Sergio, no, I don't give him permission to
Sergio no que no le doy yo permiso para
put my images, we're talking about
poner mi imágenes ya estamos hablando de
another context that is neither YouTube nor
otro contexto que no es ni YouTube ni
Twitch, we're already talking about something else,
Twitch ya estamos hablando de otra cosa
sue him because I already said that I'm
demandarlo porque ya dije yo que
going to have zero tolerance with this
tolerancia cero voy a tener con este
issue, zero tolerance, which
tema tolerancia cero que además me lo
my lawyer also told me, have zero tolerance with
dijo mi abogado ten tolerancia cero con
this issue because what has done is
este tema porque lo que ha hecho elogio
very serious praise and whatever comes, the
gravísimo y lo que venga las
ramifications that come from there, they
ramificaciones que vengan de ahí van
all come all from the Man, nothing happens here,
todas van todas de la Man pasa nada aquí
people say Yes  Yes, Sergio is
dice gente Sí sí está Sergio está Sergio
here, Sergio, would you talk to him? Yes, he is here, I
aquí tú hablarías con él ch si está aquí
understand that he will be willing to
entiendo que él estará dispuesto a
talk to you, not that he will talk
hablar contigo no que él luego hable yo
to him later, I have nothing to talk about, why am I
con él no tengo nada que hablar por qué
going to explain it to you? Why am I going to
te lo voy a explicar el Por qué te voy a
explain it to you later what happened during his
explicar luego lo que sucedió durante su
live stream? I tell him that I do not give him
directo le digo que que no le doy
permission to post the image, he has it
permiso para poner la imagen él tiene
posted in his chat that you have to follow him and
puesto en su chat que hay que seguirlo y
5 minutes to be able to write a message, there is no
5 minutos para poder escribir un mensaje
problem, those are his rules. There is no
no hay ningún problema son sus normas No
problem at all. I wait
hay ninguna clase de problema me espero
5 minutes, his moderators greet me,
5 minutos me saludan los moderadores
which one of his moderators greets. Hello,
suyos que saludo un moderador suyo Hola
sasel, with which a moderator has seen
sasel con lo cual un moderador ha visto
the message, they extend the amount of time
el mensaje amplían la cantidad de tiempo
to 30 minutes because they know that I am
a 30 minutos porque saben que estoy yo
in it, that is what happens, I wait the
en el eso es lo que sucede me espero los
30 minutes that they see that I am still there and that I am
30 minutos de que ven que sigo ahí y que
not amused by what is happening, I am not
no me hace gracia lo que está pasando
amused at all by this whole
que no me hace ninguna gracia todo este
issue, I do not understand at all, the attitude of
tema que no comprendo nada la actitud de
a straight white guy with what has
un tío blanco hetero con lo que ha
happened with Eulogio, which is that I am freaking out
pasado con lo Eulogio que es que que yo
with the reaction
flipo en colores con con con la reacción
of this boy freaking out, I did not
de este muchacho flipando no me no me
imagine Eulogio  in is to Eulogio but
imaginaba a Eulogio en es a Eulogio pero
also to a white guy who
también a un tío blanco etero que
also I say but Why does this
tampoco Digo yo pero Por qué este
guy Now he has to act like this man
muchacho Ahora tiene que ponerse así tío
leave me alone and leave my girlfriend alone she's
déjame en paz y deja en paz a mi novia
already man with your life that I also haven't
que ya está tío con tu vida que tampoco
told you that I simply told you
te he dicho que simplemente te he dicho
that I don't want to put I soundproof
que no quiero poner yo insonorizar lo de
the room and the guy gets excited and
la habitación y el tío se viene arriba y
gets excited Okay about the 30
se viene arriba Okay lo de los 30
minutes I wait 30 minutes I'm going to
minutos me espero los 30 minutos voy a
write immediately puts in
escribir pone inmediatamente en modo
emoticon mode do you see that normal I
emoticono tú eso lo ves normal te
ask you to see but to see a
pregunto a ti a ver pero a ver una
move I mean you enter Sergio's chat
movida O sea tú entras en el chat de
when Sergio is reacting to
Sergio cuando Sergio está reaccionando a
your response and I tell him the phrase I don't
tu respuesta y le digo yo la frase no te
give you permission to put my images
doy permiso para que ponga mis imágenes
in your Direct I put it like that then he
en tu Direct lo pongo así que luego él
can decide what he wants of
ya puede decidir lo que quiera por
course he can do what he wants
supuesto él ya puede hacer lo que quiera
with his life but I put it on him I can't
con su vida pero yo se lo pongo no se lo
put it first in the chat after
puedo poner de primera en el chat a los
5 minutes I put it on him he already has
5 minutos se lo pongo él ya ya tiene
proof his moderators have
constancia sus moderadores tienen
proof because it is that he responds to me 30
constancia porque es que me responde 30
minutes later I put it on him again
minutos más tarde se lo vuelvo a poner
Put the mode  emoticon and that
Pon el modo emoticono y de que se
the emoticon mode ends I put it back on
termina el modo emoticono se lo vuelvo a
and put it in the chat Hey I'm
poner y le pongo en el chat Oye estoy
freaking out with everything that's happening
flipando con todo lo que está pasando
of course everyone the whole chat eh
por supuesto todo todo el chat eh todo
the whole chat already telling me everything yeah Well
el chat ya diciéndome de todo sí Bueno
but you know that we are not responsible Let's
pero tú sabes que no somos responsables
see yoo Look for example in your chat
A ver yoo Mira por ejemplo en tu chat
right now in your chat at most there will be
ahora mismo en tu chat como mucho habrá
one or two people Like this one and another one that was there
una o dos personas Li este y otro que
But there are no more people who are
había Pero no hay más personas que me
insulting me right now their chat
esten ahora mismo insultando su chat
was all at least but look at me right now I
eran todos al menos pero mira yo ahora
have YouTube open too and I
mismo Tengo abierto YouTube también y no
'm not even seeing what they're posting
estoy ni viendo lo que están poniendo
but one thing let's see It seems to me that it's
pero una cosa vamos a ver Me parece que
getting too deep maybe the
que está calando demasiado a lo mejor el
subject of Sergio I mean me you and I
tema de lo de Sergio o sea yo tú y yo
have well the three of us have hair on our
tenemos bueno los tres tenemos pelo en
balls we are 40 tacos damn
los [__] tenemos 40 tacos [__]
Listen to it let it come up and maybe he
Escúchalo déjalo Que suba y a lo mejor
wants to clarify his position with you regarding
quiere aclarar postura contigo respecto
the subject of what he told you and No
al tema de lo que te ha dicho y No
wait wait Javi you still don't
espérate espérate Javi s que todavía no
know everything man I'll continue explaining to you I
lo sabes todo hombre te sigo explicando
put that again in the chat everything comes
vuelvo a poner eso en el chat todo viene
from the subject of the lodge  and I get kicked out by the
del tema del logio y se me expulsa los
chat moderators and the moderators
moderador chat y los moderadores me
kick me out of the chat for telling him no no no no no no Why
echan del chat por decirle que no no no
why Because what
no no no Por qué por qué Porque lo que
a straight white guy starts saying goes up
un tío blanco etero empieza a decir sube
like you said Now he goes up to my
como tú has dicho Ahora sube a mi
live or talks to me privately in
directo o habla conmigo por privado en
a whisper he kicks me out of the chat because I don't
un susurro me echa del chat porque no le
pay attention to him because I wasn't there either I was
hago caso porque tampoco estaba yo
just posting that message he kicks me out
simplemente ponía ese mensaj me echa
okay okay how can I see that you're already
vale de acuerdo como veo que que ya
very helpless because of the situation that's
mucha impotencia por la situación que
going on I say Well then he's going to
está pasando digo yo Bueno pues se va a
find out I'm going to do it right now I
enterar voy a hacer yo ahora mismo
open a live I say I don't give you
directo abro directo digo que no te doy
permission that I don't give you permission Cucu cucu I don't
permiso que no te doy permiso Cucu cucu
give you permission to post
que no te doy permiso para que pongas
any images that you can see that
ninguna imagen eso eso lo puedes ver tú
perfectly well No I don't believe you I believe you in
perfectamente No no te creo Te creo en
the live that I did in the penultimate
el directo que hice yo en el penúltimo
live that says that I don't give you that I'm not
directo que dice que no te doy que no te
going to give you that I don't you I couldn't
voy a dar yo que no te no me podía
communicate in his chat like I don't give you
comunicar en su chat tal que no te doy
permission immediately a straight white guy
permiso inmediatamente un tío blanco
directly closes the live
etero directamente cierra el directo
then deletes it or deletes his live in a way that I don't care there
luego lo borra o borra su directo manera
are people who say no it's that it
que me da igual hay gente que dice no es
's a lie and such if I have all the
que es mentira y tal si tengo todas las
screenshots  from your chat and the
capturas de su chat y de las respuestas
moderators' answers he's going to tell me
de los moderadores a mí me va a decir
if I'm lying or that I don't have all the
que si es menti o que no tengo todas las
answers right I start straight and I
respuestas bien empiezo yo directo y
start explaining the situation that
empiezo a explicar la situación que
I'm freaking out with a white guy and a
estoy flipando con un tío blanco y un
Blanc guy etero goes to the chat gets into my
tío Blanc etero va al chat se mete en mi
chat and goes all out Javi he's going
chat y va por todas Javi es que va por
all out man eh he starts again with
todas hombre eh empieza otra vez con lo
the moans he keeps insisting he starts he
de los gemidos mi sigue insistiendo Me
starts to provoke me in a very
empieza me empieza a provocar de muy
bad way he gets excited and provokes me
mala manera se viene arriba y me provoca
in a very bad way and you can
de muy mala manera y eso tú lo puedes
see it perfectly in yesterday's live
ver perfectamente en el directo de ayer
in my image how I behave and how
en mi imágen cómo me comporto yo y cómo
he behaves in the chat in the chat he
se comporta él en el chat en el chat él
calls the whole chat mongoos to the whole
llama todo el chat mongolos a todo el
chat I'm mongoos here what happens such
chat soy unos mongolos aquí que pase tal
and such not only does he call them mongoos but
y cual no solo le dice mongolos sino que
he also says another insult
le dice también otra otro improperio
as well quite a lot he starts to mess with
también bastante se empieza a meter con
people in particular he starts to want to
la gente en concreto empieza a querer
mess with everyone so that
meterse con todo el mundo para que la
people jump on him and to play the victim
gente le salte y para hacerse la víctima
to have something to hold on to to
para tener algo él a lo que aferrarse
play the victim of something and I don't
para hacerse la víctima de algo y no
understand this guy's attitude I don't  I
comprendo yo la actitud de este tipo no
understand, I thought a straight white guy was a
lo comprendo yo le tenía a un tío blanco
different kind of person, but he's
etero por otra clase de persona pero que
already shown me what he needed to show me,
a mí ya me ha demostrado lo que me tenía
the kind of person he is,
que demostrar la clase de persona que es
and the whole time I was telling him on
y todo el rato di y yo diciéndole en el
live that you should apologize
directo que le pidas perdón ahora mismo
to my girlfriend right now, no, such, and what he says
a mi novia que no tal Y que cual dice
was moaning like and he gets all like that, I mean,
estaba gimiendo como y se pone así en
the chat continued
ese plan o sea é el chat ha continuado
with the moaning. Yes, because he was
con lo de los gemidos Sí porque estaba
like really angry and like really like,
como muy enfadado y como muy tal a
listen to me, you told me what I think is what it
escúchame tú me has dicho yo lo que creo
is, and I, as advice, it's worth a
yo que es lo y yo como consejo vale como
lot of controversies that I have the same as you. I
muchas polémicas que llevo igual que tú
mean, you told me a while ago that you
O sea tú me has contado un rato que le
told the olog: Hey, I want to see you
dijiste al olog Oye tengo ganas de verte
and tell you to your face, eh. And let's see if you can
y decirte a la cara eh Y a ver si me
explain to me the same thing you're saying about
explicas lo mismo que estás diciendo de
me, about my girlfriend, she's here utbh
de mi de mi novia está aquí utbh
asking to go up and she's asking me to go up, I
pidiendo subir y me está pidiendo subir
mean, I think that, it would look really bad if you did
o sea yo creo que Quedaría muy mal que
n't want to see him on the
no quisieras verte con él en la el
video call now and he tells you: Hey,
videollamada ahora y que él te diga Oye
yes, or well, I'm not going to keep the moans up or
pues sí o pues no mantengo los gemidos o
no.  I'll keep them no no he already looked bad
no los mantengo no no él ya quedó mal
because he didn't let me talk in his chat and
con que no me dejó hablar en su chat y
that he behaved the way he behaved in mine
que se comportó como se comportó en mi
and I didn't throw him out I didn't throw him out I held on
chat y yo no le eché yo no le eché
neutral that it's neither yours nor his
aguanté neutro que no es ni el tuyo ni
here in mine we put it in water water
el de es aquí en el mío lo metemos agu
okay I put up with the whole downpour
agu de acuerdo aguanté todo el chaparrón
with this guy with the nonsense he
con este señor con las tonterías que
was saying no yes put it in but I'm
estaba diciendo no sí mételo pero yo ya
leaving I don't want to I don't even want to see his
me voy no quiero no quiero ni verle la
face I don't want to see his face or hear him I don't even want to
cara no quiero ni verle la cara ni oírle
hear him listen to me I don't know c I don't
no quiero ni oírle escúchame no se c no
know stubborn maybe he's going to take it back
se cabezón que a lo mejor va retirarlo
from the moans and he's going to clear it up for you guys [ __ ] it's
de los gemidos y te lo va a aclarar
not closed wait
[__] no est están cerrado espérate
because maybe he's going to clear it up for you
porque a lo mejor él te va a aclarar
man if he continues with the moaning thing
hombre si sigue con lo de los gemidos
well I understand your upset but I
pues entiendo tu disgusto pero yo me
imagine that he'll have found out
imagino que se habrá enterado ahora
right now not that those aren't moans
mismo mismo no de que eso no son gemidos
but that they were screams How is he going to get upset
sino que eran gritos Cómo se va entar
right now if I tell him like 15 times
ahora mismo si se lo digo como 15 veces
yesterday and he starts saying that they are moans that they
ayer y él empieza que son gemidos que
are moans simply to provoke me
son gemido simplemente para provocarme
sure seriously dude you're telling me
seguro en serio tío tú me estás diciendo
that but he Knowing knowing that
eso pero él Sabiendo sabiendo que
knowing if I explained it to him such and such and again and again and again and again and again
sabiendo si se lo expliqué tal y cual y
and it was just to
otra vez y simplemente era para
provoke me if you see the images Javi and you
provocarme si tú ves las imágenes Javi y
see his reactions it's
ves las reacciones suyas es que es
incredible but well but well it's that it
increíble pero bueno pero bueno es que
seems incredible to me because man
es que me parece increíble porque hombre
For example at the beginning what I
Yo por ejemplo al principio lo que te he
told you when I saw the clicks
dicho yo cuando he visto los click
the Editors were sending I
estaban mandando los Editores les he
told them let's see the context of this no and they
dicho a ver dme el contexto de esto no y
started sending me of course the
han empezado a mandarme claro los
titles and such Well if you don't know the If
títulos y tal Pues si tú no sabes el Si
you don't know the mess If you don't know the mess
tú no sabes el lío Si tú no sabes el lío
Well he says host Well maybe you
Pues dice [__] Pues a lo mejor tú
know what I come to think I say how
sabes lo que yo llego a pensar digo como
the kid is dedicated to a lifan I say
se dedica la chaval a un lifan digo a lo
maybe he's making
mejor está haciendo contenido
video call content or some move and it
videollamada o alguna movidad esta y se
can be misinterpreted you know but man
puede malinterpretar sabes pero hombre
your followers have already come here to
ya me han venido aquí seguidores tuyos a
tell me Javi that no that it is cut and
decirme Javi que no que está recortado y
that he was really playing
que de verdad que estaba jugando al
fortnite then I said [ __ ] well Okay
fortnite entonces he dicho yo [__]
let's go that I did what is
pues Vale vamos que he hecho lo que es
what I've done is start the
lo que he hecho ha sido volver a iniciar
extract again to comment on it from scratch
el el extracto para comentarlo de cero
so that there are no people who are left with
para que no haya gente que se quede con
the beginning you know but that but that's
el principio sabes pero eso pero eso es
what you have done but a straight white guy did
lo que has hecho tú pero un tío blanco
n't do that a straight white guy didn't
etero no hizo eso un tío blanco etero no
do that straight white guy has taken that for
hizo eso tío blanco etero ha dar por
granted more than 10 times saying I
hecho más de 10 veces eso diciendo Yo
clearly wasn't doing that
claramente que no estaba haciendo eso
So like starting like some
Entonces como una como entablar como una
kind of stupid schoolyard discussion
especie de discusión estúpida de patio
yes no yes no man what why is he
de colegio que sí que no que sí que no
telling me no I don't
tío que qué que por qué está diciéndome
know what you're about why is he
que no que que no sé de qué vas que por
trying to get me involved I don't understand you I don't
qué te está intentando meter conmigo que
understand you it
no te entiendo que no te comprendo que
's that I don't know about this subject eh Why did you
es que no sé en este tema eh Por qué te
want to fight with me But anyway
has querido zarzar conmigo Pero bueno ya
Sergio will send you the link by
está Sergio te manda el enlace por
WhatsApp Tell me that then
WhatsApp Échame cuenta que entonces
then in the end this has escalated to the point
entonces al final esto ha escalado en
that the loggio is out of the equation and in the
que lo logio se sale de la ecuación y al
end you no no leaves no no no no no no
final tú no no se va no no no no no no
the equation It's always the same the
la ecuación Siempre es la misma la
equation is the same There is no
ecuación es la misma No hay ninguna
equation outside, I mean the apologies of deio
ecuación fuera o sea las disculpas deio
you don't accept them no  under no
tú no la no las aceptas no bajo ningún
circumstances is it that they are not an excuse.
concepto es que no son ni disculpa De
Let's see, Javi, I haven't
nada vamos a ver Javi que no te lo no te
told you, eh, that the same day that
lo he contado eh que el mismo día en el
I do the live video of
que yo hago el directo del vídeo de
Eulogio that Eulogio does a live
Eulogio que el Eulogio hace directo
talking about the subject eh And that he also
hablando sobre el tema eh Y que también
gets very excited because here
se viene muy arriba porque aquí toda la
everyone is getting very excited Eh
gente est es que se viene muy arriba Eh
and they get very excited and say no Well, I would
y se viene muy arriba y dice no Bueno yo
n't do it again but I don't
no lo volvería a hacer pero no me
regret it
arrepiento
[Music]
[Música]